爸爸走了
Look, dad's gone now.
我们得继承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
那就是
And that means hunting down
能猎杀多少凶鬼恶灵杀多少
as many evil sons of bitches as we possibly can.
(忆往昔)
发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
那是魔鬼之门  地狱的大门
That's a Devil's Gate, a damn door to hell.
你有多确定
How certain are you
你复活的
that what you brought back...
是百分百纯粹的萨姆
is 100 percent pure Sam?
告诉我你是谁
Just tell me who you are.
- 那不重要  - 告诉我你是谁
- It doesn't matter. - Just tell me who you are!
你是个恶魔
You're a demon.
我想时不时帮帮你
I wanna help you from time to time.
你为什么想帮我
Why would you wanna help me?
我能帮你救你哥哥
I could help you save your brother.
1835年
Back in 1835,
萨穆埃尔·柯尔特造了把特别的枪
Samuel Colt made a special gun.
这枪能杀任何东西
This gun can kill anything.
(如今)
还有一本
One more.
今晚就这样吧  修女
That's all for tonight, Sister.
来吧  我送你回车上
Come on. Let me walk you to your car.
神父
Father?
安迪
Andy?
神父
Father...
上帝离开我们了
God's not with us.
他不在了
Not anymore.
安迪  他当然还在
Andy, of course he is.
你为什么要这么说  出什么事了
Why would say that? What's wrong?
他帮不了我们
He can't help us.
即便他能
And if he can...
他也不肯帮
he won't.
安迪  等等
Andy, wait!
[邪恶力量 第3季第4集]
怎么了
What's up?
我可能在俄亥俄州发现了预兆
Might've found some omens in Ohio.
无雨闪电
Dry lightning,
气压骤降
barometric pressure drop.
令人兴奋
That's thrilling.
还有个家伙在教堂里崩了自己的脑袋
Plus, some guy blows his head off in a church
另一个则在一家消闲品店里发了狂
and another goes postal in a hobby shop
然后被警察击毙了
before the cops take him out.
可能是恶魔预兆
Might be demonic omens.
也可能只是普通的自杀和喜欢拼贴簿的疯子
Or it could just be a suicide and a psycho scrapbooker.
嗯  但这是林肯后我们最好的线索
Yeah. But it's our best lead since Lincoln.
俄亥俄哪里
Where in Ohio?
伊丽莎白维尔
Elizabethville.
是铁锈地带一个衰败的工厂镇
It's a half-dead factory town in the rust belt.
南海滩就没有恶魔吗
There's gotta be a demon or two in South Beach.
抱歉  花花公子  下次吧
Sorry, Hef, maybe next time.
怎么样了  鲍比
How's it going, Bobby?
进展缓慢
Slow.
跟你说
Man, I tell you,
看到柯尔特枪这样子有点让人难过
it's a little sad seeing the Colt like that.
它现在唯一的用处
Well, the only thing it's good for now,
就是研究明白它的原理
is figuring out what makes it tick.
它的原理是什么
So, what makes it tick?
如果我们要去俄亥俄州看看这些预兆
So if we wanna go check out these omens in Ohio...
你下午之前能把那玩意修好吗
you think you can have that thing ready by this afternoon?
到那时是杀不了恶魔
Well, it won't kill demons by then,
但我保证能杀了你
but I can promise you it'll kill you.
好吧  走  我们在浪费日光呢
All right. Come on. We're wasting the daylight.
回见  鲍比
See you, Bobby.
你们如果遇见了什么
You boys run into anything,
不论什么
anything,
都联系我
you call me.
没什么可供保险公司调查的
There's not much left for the insurance company.
那就是起自杀  我亲眼所见
It was a suicide. Saw it myself.
那这应该很快就能结束了
Well, this shouldn't take long, then.
安迪就在那里动手的
That's where Andy did it.
那是我几周来第一次见他
It's the first time I'd seen him in weeks.
他以前每周日都来
He used to come every Sunday.
他什么时候不再来了
When did he stop?
大概两个月前吧
Probably about two months ago.
就在其他一切开始变化的时候
Right around the time everything else started to change.
怎么变化了
Change how?
这么说吧  这以前是座让人骄傲的小镇
Let's just say this used to be a town you could be proud of.
人们关心彼此
People cared about each other.
安迪还是唱诗班成员
Andy sang in the choir.
但有一天  他突然就不再是安迪了
And then one day he just wasn't Andy anymore.
就好像他...
It was like he was...
被附身了吗
Possessed?
可以这么说吧
You could say that.
把钱赌光了
Gambled away his money,
背着妻子出轨
cheated on his wife,
毁了自己的生意
destroyed his business.
是啊
Yes.
就像一个开关被扳动了
Like a switch had flipped.
神父  你认识那个
Father, did you know the man
在消闲品店里杀人的人吗
who killed those folks in the hobby shop?
当然  托尼·珀金斯
Sure, Tony Perkins.
托尼·珀金斯
Tony Perkins.
好人
Good man.
你觉得他也是有天突然性情大变吗
Would you say that his personality suddenly changed one day too?
我从未那么想过  但是
I never thought about it that way but...
是的
yes.
跟安迪一样  大概是两个月前突然变了
About the same time as Andy, about two months ago.
谢谢  神父
Well, thank you, Father.
多谢你抽时间
Appreciate your time.
两个月前  我们打开了魔鬼之门
Two months ago, we opened up the Devil's Gate...
而这小镇突然就变成了堕落之城吗
all of a sudden this town turns into Margaritaville?
绝不是巧合
It's no coincidence.
里奇
Richie.
难以置信
I don't believe it.
迪恩·温彻斯特  是吧
Dean Winchester, right?
- 嗯  - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
这是我妹妹
This is my sister...
雪莉
Cheryl.
给
Here.
那个...
Well, you know,
是继妹
stepsister.
来吧  这是我弟弟  萨姆
Come on in. This is my brother, Sam.
- 你好吗  - 还好
- How you doing? - Not too bad.
嗯
Yeah.
你俩怎么认识的
How do you two know each other?
你当时在上学
You were in school.
是卡纳西的那个梦魔  是吧
It was that succubus in Canarsie, right?
对
Yeah, yeah.
天啊  你真该看到那妞的奶子
Man. You should have seen the rack on this broad.
我不得不干掉她  真是悲剧啊
Frigging tragedy when I had to gank her.
等等  是谁杀了她
Wait. Who...? Who killed her?
如果我没记错  是我及时救场  你才保住命
If I remember your ass was toast until I showed up.
我都忘了这家伙多会说笑话了
I forgot what a comedian this guy was.
里奇  我当时就跟你说过  现在再说一次
Richie, Richie, you know, I told you then, I'll tell you again.
你不适合这工作
You're not cut out for this job.
你会害死自己的
You're gonna get yourself killed.
说
Talk to me.
对了  温彻斯特  恶语伤人
FYI, Winchester. Words hurt.
嗯
Yeah.
不  现在不方便  亲爱的  回头的
No, it's not a good time, baby. Later.
你在这镇上有发现吗
So you find anything in this town anyway?
没有
No, I got nothing.
等等  你是指恶魔什么的吗
Wait a minute, you mean as in demons and whatnot?
- 对  - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我没发现
No, I got nothing.
不出所料
Typical.
那你刚刚那位妹妹呢
What about your sister back there?
说实话
Honestly?
她体内绝对有魔鬼
She definitely had the devil in her.
但她不是恶魔  你明白我的意思吗
But she wasn't no demon. You know what I'm saying?
嗯
Right.
说真的
Seriously,
教堂男  消闲品店男
church guy, hobby-shop guy,
等我赶到时  他们都死透透了
they were lunch meat by the time I got there.
或许他们是被附身了  但我无法证明
Maybe they were possessed, but I can't prove it.
是啊  我们也面临这情况
Yeah, that's where we are too.
假如说
You know what, let's just say that
恶魔是附身了这镇上的人
demons are possessing people in this town,
- 到处搞事  - 嗯
- you know, raising hell... - Yeah.
但恶魔为什么要崩了自己的脑袋
But why would a demon blow his brains out?
图好玩吗
For fun?
毁坏一具身体  再转攻下一具
You know, he wrecks one body, moves to another.
就像开偷来的车兜风
You know, like taking a stolen car for a joyride.
这镇上还有符合这个特征的人吗
Anybody else left in town fits that profile?
好人突然变渣  还活着的
You know, nice guy turned douche, still breathing?
有特洛特
There's Trotter.
那是谁
Who's that?
他原本是扶轮社主席
Well, he used to be head of the rotary club.
然后人们说他突然变成了个混蛋
And then people say he turned bastard all the sudden.
带来了赌博和妓女
Brought in the gambling, the hookers.
这整座小镇现在基本都属于他了
He practically owns this whole town.
知道我们可以去哪找他吗
You know where we could find him?
他几小时后就会去他的酒吧
He'll be at his bar in a few hours.
(酒吧)
你不是说这是座落魄的工厂镇吗
I thought you said this was some boarded-up factory town.
是啊
It is.
至少本该是的
Or at least it's supposed to be.
我们还等什么  去调研一番吧
Well, what are we waiting for? Let's do some research.
(特洛特酒吧)
里奇  看看你
Richie, look at you.
复兴缎子衣服了
Bringing satin back.
你喜欢吗
You like this?
去运河街的泰国丝绸看看
Try Thai Silk. Canal Street.
这样的衣服少说也300美元
You have to pay $300 for threads like these, easy.
当然了  对于我  别说了
Of course, to me? Forget about it.
"别说了"是多少钱
How much is "forget about it"?
别说了
Forget about it.
那就是特洛特
That's Trotter over there.
他整晚都坐在那里
He sits there all night.
- 别想靠近他  - 我们现在怎么办
- Can't touch him. - So, what do we do now?
我不知道你们怎么想
Don't know about you guys,
但我要去找那酒保调查一下
but I'm gonna do a little investigating with that bartender.
别急
Easy.
我和她  我们...
Me and her, we got a little
说好稍后一起玩玩了
something-something lined up for later.
得了吧
Yeah, right.
不爽吧
Stings, don't it?
好吧  我去解手了
All right, I gotta hit the head.
释放下人质
Release the hostages.
马上回来
Be back in a few.
他才不可能泡到那样的姑娘  看看她
No way he gets a girl like that. I mean, look at her.
那屁股能放在五分硬币上了
You could fit that ass on a nickel.
是吗
You think so?
抱歉  神父
Sorry, Padre.
就知道你们会找来这里  每个人都不免俗
Knew you boys would find your way here. They all do.
无意冒犯
No offense...
但您怎么会在这里  神父
but what are you doing here, Father?
不管怎样  神父要去信众所在的地方
Like it or not, you go where your flock is.
- 而且神父喝酒不要钱  - 是啊
- Plus the clergy drinks for free. - True.
某个酒保还欠我一次忏悔
And a certain bartender owes me a confession.
这辈子别想了  神父
Not in this lifetime, Father.
你周日最好过来
I better see your butt on Sunday.
不管有没有硬币
Nickel or no nickel.
你们需要点什么
What can I get you boys?
你们的招牌酒是什么
What's your specialty?
我很会调飓风
I make a mean hurricane.
那我就试试吧
I guess we'll see about that.
- 你还喝飓风  - 现在喝了
- You drink hurricanes? - I do now.
- 约翰  - 雷吉
- John. - Reggie.
- 你没事吧  - 我不知道
- Everything okay with you? - I don't know.
我今天感觉不太自在
I'm just not feeling myself today.
救命
Help!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
他睡了我老婆
He slept with my wife.
那混蛋睡了我老婆
The bastard slept with my wife.
谁快报警
Somebody call 911.
手放后
Behind your back.
这里警察太多了  我们跑吧
Too many cops here, I say we bolt.
淡定
Just be cool.
可怜虫
Poor jerk.
他就是被半打啤酒附身了
Only thing possessing him was a sixer of Pabst.
到底怎么回事
So, what's the deal, then?
这小镇里的人究竟有没有被附身
People in this town getting possessed or not?
我不知道  或许就真像看上去那么简单
I don't know. Maybe it is just what it is, you know.
只是个人渣小镇
A town full of scumbags.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
你们准备好拍大头照了吗
You boys ready for your mug shots?
摄影师马上就到
Photographer's gonna be here in a few and
给你们拍照登在本地报纸上
take your picture for the local paper.
很荣幸  警官  太让人兴奋了
Be an honor, officer. What a thrill.
嗯  我们该走了
Yup, time to go.
等等
Wait a second. Wait a second.
怎么了
What?
里奇呢
Where's Richie?
一个酒保怎么买得起这样的房子
So how's a bartender afford a place like this?
我父母留给我的
My parents left it to me.
我不怎么来这里
I don't come out here much.
除非是想单独待着
Mostly when I wanna be alone.
这里  不错啊
This is, uh, charming.
你不觉得找间卧室会更惬意吗
You sure you wouldn't be more comfortable in a bedroom?
或者去我的旅馆房间
Or, uh, my motel room?
不说别的  但我有精油
I mean, not for nothing. But, you know, I got oils.
但我有玩具
But I have toys.
嗯  玩具比精油好
Yeah, no, toys trump oils.
你自己待在这下面不害怕吗
You don't, uh, get scared down here all by yourself?
当然不
Of course not.
毕竟还有个猎人会保护我
Not when I've got a hunter to protect me.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道你眼前有红肉吧
You do realize there's red meat within striking distance, right?
我还得跟里奇说多少次
How many times I gotta tell Richie
他会害自己惹上麻烦的
he's gonna get himself in trouble?
迪恩  你认定他是失踪了
Dean, you're assuming he's missing.
但他可能只是跑了
I mean, maybe he just bailed.
他是个白痴
He's a moron.
他是个可爱的白痴  但他不是懦夫
I mean, he's a sweet moron, but he's not a coward.
他不会就那么跑了的
He wouldn't just bail.
- 我得去找到他  - 好吧
- I gotta go find him. - All right.
我现在要去跟踪这个特洛特
Meanwhile, I think I'm gonna trail this Trotter guy.
- 是吗  - 嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我不知道
I don't know.
他昨晚看我的眼神有点怪怪的
Something about the way he looked at me last night.
或许这里真有什么古怪
Maybe there is something going on here.
枪不错
Cute piece.
你是谁
Who are you?
打不死恶魔的  如果那是你的目标
Won't stop a demon if that's what you think.
你怎么知道
How the hell would you know?
怎么说呢
I don't know.
算是合理推测吧
Call it an educated guess.
那我真走运
Well, ain't I lucky, then?
有试枪的靶子了
Found a subject for a test fire.
这跟运气毫无关系
Luck had nothing to do with it.
但是
But,
请便  尽管来吧
by all means, take your best shot.
你是要像个怂包似的站在那里
Are you gonna stand there like a pantywaist
还是要打...
or are you gonna shoot...?
有点疼呢
This smarts a little.
你想要什么
What do you want?
世界和平
Peace on earth.
新衣服
A new shirt.
你到底要不要我帮你修枪
Now, do you want me to help you out with that gun or not?
- 迪恩  - 萨姆
- Dean. - Sammy.
我现在没法说话
Yeah, I can't talk right now.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯  我没事
Yeah, I'm fine. Just
20分钟后我们酒吧见  好吗
meet me at the bar in 20 minutes. Okay?
萨姆
Sam?
我得告诉你...
I gotta tell you...
这地方的每个女人
every woman in this place...
都对你垂涎三尺
they wanna eat you up.
哎呀
Well, hey.
任何人都可能擒住那人
Anybody could've tackled that guy.
夺下他的枪
And wrestled the gun away.
阻止他大开杀戒
Prevented mass murder.
这样吧
Here's what I'm gonna do.
我一般每晚收费400美元
Normally, I charge 400 a night.
我给你打个五折  我们离开这里吧
Why don't we call it an even deuce and get the hell out of here?
你当我是什么
What do I look like?
小气鬼
Cheapskate.
你是被妓女嫌弃了吗
Did I just see you strike out with a prostitute?
怎么回事啊
How's that work?
我就告诉她我对酒保有意思
Just told her I had a thing for the bartender.
很简单
It was pretty easy.
谁说酒保有空了
Who says the bartender's available?
好问题
That's a good question.
你是跟谁约好了吗
You got something going with some guy,
大概这么高  穿件运动衫
you know, about yay tall, wears a sweat suit?
谁
Who?
没谁
No.
我错了
My mistake.
你下班后我们去喝一杯吧
What do you say you and me grab a drink after your shift?
为什么要等呢
I say, why wait...
我们现在就能走
when we can go right now?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我觉得你可能知道
I think maybe you know.
是吗
Yeah?
我觉得我要报警
Well, I think I'm calling the cops.
- 报警  - 擅闯  袭人
- Cops? - Breaking and entering, assault.
你麻烦大了  朋友
You're in a peck of trouble, my friend.
我或许能解释
Well, I think I could probably explain.
好  退后
All right, back up.
- 退后  - 钱在保险箱里
- Get back. - Money's in the safe.
拿上走吧
Take it and go.
我不要你的钱
I don't want your money.
但我得确认一下
I just gotta be sure.
- 你是什么疯子啊  - 天啊
- What kind of psycho are you? - God.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这可能只是个小误会
I think that this was just a minor misunderstanding.
嗯  好吧
Yeah, okay.
那我...还是走吧
How about I just...? I just leave, because...
我把这个拿走
I'll take these.
这个...
Okay, I'II,
我留下了
I'll leave this for...
给你们
you.
祝你们愉快
Have a nice day?
看来女佣今天放假了
Looks like the maid's day off.
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
你随意点
Make yourself comfortable.
我忘了说了
I forgot to mention.
里奇是我的朋友
Richie was a friend of mine.
我发现我能追踪他手机的定位系统
When I realized I could track the GPS in his cell phone,
于是我之前来了一趟
I swung by earlier.
好好安葬了他
Gave him a proper burial.
总比在一个贱货地下室里发霉好
It's better than rotting in some skank's basement.
真扫兴啊
Isn't that a buzz kill?
抱歉了  妹子
Sorry, sister...
但你要回老家了
but you're going back to where you came from.
我看不会
I don't think so.
你笑什么  贱人
What are you laughing at, bitch?
你还是被困着
You're still trapped.
你也是
So are you.
贱人
Bitch.
丢东西了吗
Lose something?
你们这些恶魔嘴巴真贱
Well, you demons have such smart mouths.
这是天赋
It's a gift.
是啊
Yeah, well.
等我送你回地狱  看你还笑得出不
Let's see if you're smiling when I send your ass back to hell.
没了你的驱魔书你还能做到吗
Without your little exorcism book?
来啊
Go ahead.
记不起来了吗  伙计
Having a little trouble there, sport?
想得美  但你好像刚叫了披萨
Nice try, but I think you just ordered a pizza.
看来你上拉丁语课时该更专心点的
Guess you should've paid more attention in Latin class.
我不知道你笑个什么劲
I don't know what you're smiling about.
你哪都别想去
You're not going anywhere.
看来  你也哪都别想去
And apparently, neither are you.
是  但会有人来救我的
Yeah, but I got somebody coming for me and,
他上课时专心听了
he did pay attention in class.
是啊  萨姆
Right, Sam.
大家都说他才是你们中聪明的那个
Everyone says he's the brains of the outfit.
- 大家  - 对
- Everyone? - Sure,
你们温家兄弟很有名
you Winchester boys are famous.
- 没有洛翰那么有名  但是...  - 呵呵
- Not Lohan famous, but, you know. - Well,
真荣幸呢
that's flattering.
等萨姆来了  我一定转告他
Yeah. I'll be sure to let Sam know when he gets here.
如果是他先来
If he shows up first.
怎么  你以为我是一个人吗
What, you thought I was flying solo?
不该低估敌人  迪恩  你可能因此而死
Shouldn't underestimate, Dean. It might be the death of you.
随你怎么瞪我
You can give me hard eyes all you want...
但事实就是
but the fact remains,
我们只能等等看谁先来了
we just have to wait and see who shows up first.
是救兵
The cavalry
还是印第安人
or the Indians.
你看上去好紧张
You look kind of tense.
知道吗
You know...
我知道种保准让你放松的办法
I know a sure-fire way to relax.
回头的吧
Maybe later.
不好意思
Excuse me?
需要点什么
What can I get for you?
记得昨晚跟我一起来的男人吗
You remember the guy I was with last night?
我们当时就坐在这里
We sat right here.
那个扑倒雷吉的大英雄
The big hero who jumped on Reggie.
对  那个...
Yeah, yeah. The...
大英雄  对
The big hero, right.
你今天见过他吗
Have you seen him around at all today?
或许吧  看情况了
Maybe, depends.
看什么情况
Depends on what?
天啊
My...
这镇上每个人都要钱吗
Does everyone here have their hand out?
他大概一小时前跟凯茜走了
He left with Casey about an hour ago.
知道他们去哪了吗
Any idea where they went?
她家  去研读圣经了
Her place, for Bible study.
好吧  你知道她的地址吗
All right, you got an address?
你什么毛病
What's wrong with you?
你觉得我会把同事的地址告诉你吗
Think I'm gonna give you a coworker's address...
好让你过去
just so can you go over there
像个变态偷窥狂似的爽一把
and get your freaky, peeping-Tom rocks off?
皮尔蒙特街和克林顿街街口
Corner of Piermont and Clinton.
祝你开心
Have fun.
你放松一下吧
Why don't you relax?
你给我去死吧
Why don't you kiss my ass?
迪恩  你是个诗人呢  我都不知道
Why, Dean, you're a poet. I had no idea.
我们是无法影响此事的结果的
Look, we won't have any effect on the outcome of this.
不如礼貌些
We might as well be civil.
礼貌吗
Civil, huh?
杀里奇  那叫礼貌吗
Killing Richie, that was...? That was civil?
他人畜无害
Guy was harmless.
他对我掏的刀
That knife he pulled on me...
看上去可不"无害"呢
didn't look harmless.
刀又伤不了你
Knife wouldn't hurt you.
对  但会损坏这具身体
No, but it would damage this body.
凯茜的身体这么美
And Casey has such a fine body.
我不想看到它被破坏
I wouldn't wanna see it ripped.
有善心的恶魔
A demon with a heart.
这镇上的好多死人
Well, you know, there's a bunch of dead people in town
不会这么看呢
that might disagree with you.
我可没扣过扳机
I didn't pull any triggers.
你是做了什么
You did something.
你想知道我做了什么吗
You wanna know what I did?
我究竟做了什么
What I really did?
我吃了顿午餐
I had lunch.
午餐
Lunch?
我和特洛特
Me and Trotter.
他点了奶酪汉堡  我点了沙拉
He had a cheeseburger. I had a salad.
我指出  他可以挣大钱
And I just pointed out the money that could be made...
只需要经营一些迎合无害恶习的生意
with a few businesses that cater to harmless vice.
特洛特照做了  他们就都来了
So Trotter built it and, man, did they come.
那些所谓的敬神的民众
Supposedly God-fearing folk,
深陷在酒精  性爱和赌博里
waist-deep in booze, sex, gambling.
我都不需要做什么
I barely lifted a finger.
就这样吗
That's it?
你不懂
You don't get it.
你只需要把人类往合适的方向推一把
All you gotta do is nudge humans in the right direction.
一点威士忌  一个妓女
Some whiskey here, a hooker there.
他们都会笑逐颜开地
And they'll walk right into hell
大步走进地狱
with big, fat smiles on their faces.
你们人类就是烂  迪恩
Your kind is corrupt, Dean.
软弱
Weak.
我们的意志更坚定
Our will is stronger.
所以我们能赢
That's why we'll win.
那就是结局吗
And that's how it ends?
不  那是开始
No, that's how it begins.
迪恩
Dean?
硫磺
Sulfur.
恶魔夺取世界吗
So demons take over?
不是说温顺的人将继承大地吗
I thought the meek shall inherit the earth.
那是你们圣经上说的
According to your Bible.
那只是本书  迪恩
It's only a book, Dean.
不是每个人都会这么看
Not everyone would agree.
因为那是上帝的书吗
Because it's God's book?
你相信上帝吗  迪恩
Do you believe in God, Dean?
如果你相信我会感到意外的
I'd be surprised if you did.
我不知道
I don't know.
我想相信
I'd like to.
我怎么不觉得你和你的上帝
Well, I don't see how you and your God
做得很好
have done such a bang-up job.
战争  种族屠杀  情况还越来越糟
War, genocide, it's only getting worse.
这一个世纪以来
I mean, in this past century,
你们制造的死亡让我们都觉得不可思议
you people racked up a body count that amazed even us.
现在轮到我们了
It's our turn now.
我们这次要做好
And we're gonna do it right this time.
别太抱希望  迪恩
Don't be hopeful, Dean.
你没获得解脱
You're not delivered.
那只是风
It's only the wind.
鲍比  是萨姆  我们有大麻烦了
Bobby, it's Sam. We got a big problem.
我发现了一些硫磺  还找不到迪恩了
I found some sulfur and now I can't find Dean.
收到后马上联系我
Call me as soon as you get this.
不好意思  他们没在那里
Excuse me. They weren't there.
看来你的改天晚上再爽了
I guess you gotta catch your jollies another night.
来
Here.
你喝一杯
Why don't you have a drink...
- 放松一下吧  - 我不想放松
- and relax? - Yeah, I don't want to relax.
这镇上的人是怎么回事啊
What is it with the people in this town?
随你了  公主
Suit yourself, princess.
神父
Father.
怎么了
Yes?
可以...跟你谈谈吗
Could I...? Can I talk to you for a sec?
你说得天花乱坠  亲爱的
You know, you're piling it pretty high there, sweetheart.
我可不怎么信
I'm not sure I'm buying.
我为什么要撒谎
Why would I lie?
恶魔就会撒谎
Demons lie.
有些是的
Some do.
也有些是真信徒
Some are true believers.
信什么
Believers in what?
怎么  你以为只有人类有更高力量吗
What, you think humans have an exclusive on a higher power?
- 你们有上帝吗  - 当然
- You have a god? - Sure.
他叫路西法
His name's Lucifer.
魔鬼吗
You mean the devil?
那是你们的用词  不是我们的
Your word, not ours.
路西法的本意是"光明使者"  自己去查
Lucifer actually means "light bringer." Look it up.
他曾是上帝天使中最美的一个
Once, he was the most beautiful of all God's angels.
但上帝要求他向人类屈膝
But God demanded that he bow down before man.
他拒绝后  便被上帝驱逐
And when he refused, God banished him.
告诉我  迪恩
Tell me, Dean,
你愿意向不如你的生物屈膝吗
how do you like bowing before lesser creatures?
路西法是真的吗
Lucifer's really real?
没人见过他
Well, no one's actually seen him.
但据说是他把我们变成了这样
But they say that he made us into what we are.
还说他会归来
And they say that he'll return.
是吗
Yeah? And,
你相信这些吗
you believe that?
我有信念
I've got faith.
你看  我们跟你们真那么不同吗
So you see? Is my kind really all that different than yours?
除了
Well, except that,
恶魔是邪恶的
you know, demons are evil.
人类就那么美好吗
And humans are such a lovable bunch.
迪克·切尼
Dick Cheney.
- 他是你们的人吗  - 还不是
- He one of yours? - Not yet.
但这么说吧  楼下有给他预留的停车位
Well, let's just say he's got a parking spot reserved for him downstairs.
说到楼下
Speaking of downstairs.
下面什么样
What's it like down there?
地狱吗
What, hell?
对
Yeah.
对了
That's right.
你那笔交易给你定了去那里的单程票
You booked a one-way ticket with that deal.
你不会喜欢的  迪恩
You're not gonna like it, Dean.
而且看你惹的那些麻烦
And, um, judging from the trouble you've caused...
你是别想住总统套房了
I don't think you'll be getting the presidential suite.
那是个绝望之坑
No, it's a pit of despair.
你以为我们为什么都想来这里
Why do you think we want to come here?
那晚那个酒保  凯茜
So the bartender the other night, Casey.
你跟她熟吗
You know her pretty well?
自她还小时就认识她了
Since she was in pigtails.
她和我哥哥
Well, um, she and my brother, they...
他们
They...
今晚走了
left tonight.
一起走的
Together.
好吧
Well...
我虽然不赞同  但他们是自愿的成年人
not that I approve, but they are consenting adults.
是啊
Right.
抱歉  你说"哥哥"
I'm sorry, you said "brother."
我以为你俩是保险调查员呢
I thought the two of you were insurance investigators.
对对  我们是的
Right. Right, well, we are.
算是家族企业吧
It's like a family business. You know?
总之
Anyways, um, so
我去过了凯茜的公寓  但他们不在那里
I went to Casey's apartment and they weren't there.
我就是感觉...
I... I just have this feeling that they...
他们可能有麻烦了
That they might be in trouble.
什么样的麻烦
What kind of trouble?
就是有麻烦了
Just trouble.
求你  神父  我需要你帮忙
Look, please, Father, I need your help.
你知道凯茜什么事吗
Is there anything you can tell me about Casey?
知道她可能去了哪吗
Any place she'd go maybe...?
是的  是有个地方  我去拿外套
Yes. There is a place. Let me get my jacket.
不  等等  神父  我不想麻烦你
No, wait, wait, Father. I don't wanna put you out.
我可以自己去
I can do this by myself.
孩子  如果凯茜真有麻烦了
Son, if Casey's really in trouble,
那就没什么好商量的了
then there's nothing to talk about.
我们走吧
Shall we go?
挺有意思的  是吧
Kind of funny, don't you think?
你和我  像一对常人一样坐在这里
You and me sitting here like a couple of regular folk.
是啊  真好笑
Yeah, it's hilarious.
有点天启的意味
You know, in that apocalyptic sort of way.
你还不错  迪恩
You're all right, Dean.
其他人可不是这么说你的
The others don't describe you that way.
但是...你挺可爱
But, you know, you're... You're likable.
一个恶魔喜欢我
A demon likes me.
抱歉  我不知道该怎么回应
Sorry, I don't know how to respond to that.
你可以说谢谢
You could say thanks.
你为救萨姆做的交易
That deal you made to save Sam?
很多其他人为此嘲讽你
A lot of others would mock you for it,
认为那是软弱或愚蠢
think it was weak or stupid.
我不这么认为
I don't.
其实还挺让人觉得解脱的
It's been kind of liberating, actually.
何必担心未来呢
And what's the point in worrying about a future...
你反正也没有未来了
when you don't have one, huh?
但不管怎么说
Still...
只剩一年了
a year to live.
你不怕吗
You're not scared?
不
No.
一点都不吗
Not even a little?
当然不
Of course not.
保险调查员啊
So insurance investigating?
你喜欢这工作吗
You enjoy the work?
嗯嗯
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I
我喜欢能帮助他人
like being able to help people.
考虑过做别的吗
Ever think about doing anything else?
比如呢
Like what?
什么都行
Anything.
你似乎很聪明
You seem like a pretty smart kid.
我觉得你是个做领头羊的料子
Somehow, I see you out in front of the pack.
你能做大事
You could do some great things.
我不知道
I don't know.
我喜欢我的工作吧
I like doing what I'm doing, I guess.
好吧  那是你的人生
Well, it's your life.
那个...
Does, um...?
- 迪恩吗  - 对  迪恩
- Dean? - Yeah, Dean.
他经常惹麻烦吗
Does he find trouble often?
是啊
Yeah.
迪恩是惹过不少麻烦
Yeah, Dean finds his fair share.
幸好他还有你
Well, it's a good thing he has you.
哥哥的守护者
His brother's keeper.
哎呦  迪恩  我要是不知道
Why, Dean, if I didn't know better,
我会以为你眼里有淫欲呢
I'd say that was lust in your eyes.
那样倒也可以消磨时间
Well, that would be one way to spend the time.
但我觉得你早上不会尊敬我的
But I don't think you'd respect me in the morning.
没关系
That's okay.
我现在也不怎么尊敬你
I mean, hey, I barely respect you now.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
我知无不言
I'm an open book.
大门开启
So the gate opened.
恶魔大军被放了出来  现在呢
The demon army was let out. What now?
我没看到你们有什么大计划
I'm not seeing a big honking plan here.
说实话吗
Honestly?
原本是有计划
There was a plan.
亚撒色是个暴君
Azazel was a tyrant...
但他把我们团结在了一起
but he held us all together.
亚撒色
Azazel?
怎么  你以为他的朋友也喊他"黄眼恶魔"吗
What, you think his friends just called him "Yellow Eyes"?
他也有名字的
He had a name.
你杀了他后  计划瓦解了
After you did him in, it all fell apart.
抱歉了
Sorry about that.
怎么  没有指挥链吗
So, what, no chain of command?
原本有
There was.
是萨姆
It was Sam.
萨姆本该成为大统领
Sam was supposed to be the Grand Pooh Bah,
带领军队  但是
lead the big army. But
他并没有承担这个责任  是吧
he hasn't exactly stepped up to the plate, has he?
感谢上帝
Thank God for that.
又提上帝
Again with God?
你觉得这是好事吗
You think this is a good thing?
现在是一片混乱  全线作战
Now you've got chaos, a war without a front.
数百个恶魔  都想争权
Hundreds of demons, all jockeying for power.
都在争夺王位
All fighting for the crown.
大部分都想灭了你弟弟
Most of them gunning for your brother.
对了
For the record...
我本是打算追随萨姆的
I was ready to follow Sam.
迪恩
Dean!
看来你赢了
Looks like you win.
迪恩
Dean!
去那边看看
Check that way.
- 萨姆  - 迪恩
- Sam. - Dean!
萨姆  这里  地下室坍塌了
Sammy, down here! The basement caved in!
迪恩  撑住了  我们就来
Dean, hey, hold on, okay? We're coming.
还有谁来了
Who's "we"?
我跟神父一起来的
I'm here with the Father.
萨姆  小心点
Sammy, be careful.
鲍比  你没事吧
Bobby, you all right?
- 你怎么知道我们...  - 快去
- How did you know where we...? - Go.
你听到了  快去
You heard the man. Go.
站住
Stop.
你俩
You two?
几世纪了
For centuries.
我们在地狱里走了个来回  毫不夸张
We've been to hell and back. Literally.
别动他
Leave him be.
别杀他  我们走吧
Don't kill him. Let's just go.
求你
Please.
萨姆  等等
Sam, wait.
你怎么看  鲍比
Well, what do you think, Bobby?
我们在这里做的事  你觉得改变什么了吗
About what we did here. Do you think it made a difference?
少了两个需要担心的恶魔
Two less demons to worry about.
那不算没什么
That's not nothing.
但特洛特还活着
Yeah, but Trotter's still alive.
人不归我们管
Humans ain't our job.
是啊  但你觉得情况会改变吗
Yeah. But you think anything's really gonna change?
或许这些人的确只想
I mean, maybe these people do just wanna
毁灭自我
really destroy themselves.
或许这场战争我们的确必输无疑
Maybe it is a losing battle.
那是你还是那恶魔女的想法
That you or that demon girl talking?
是我
It's me.
恶魔死了  它附身的辣妹也死了
The demon is dead. And so is that hot girl it was possessing.
没办法
Well, had to be done.
萨姆是想救你
Sam was saving your life.
是  但你没看到  鲍比  他好冷酷
Yeah. But you didn't see it, Bobby. He was cold.
鲍比
Bobby.
嗯
Yeah.
在怀俄明州  有那么一小会儿
Back in Wyoming, uh, there was this moment.
黄眼恶魔对我说了些话
Yellow Eyes said something to me.
他说了什么
What'd he say?
或许
That maybe when...
萨姆复活时...不管他是去了哪
Sam came back from... Well, wherever. That
或许复活的他不一样了
maybe he came back different.
怎么不一样了
Different how?
我不知道  不管怎样  听上去不妙
I don't know. Whatever it was, it didn't sound good.
你觉得...
You think...?
你觉得我弟弟是不是有毛病
You think something's wrong with my brother?
不
No.
恶魔都撒谎
Demons lie.
萨姆肯定没事的
I'm sure Sam's okay.
嗯
Yeah.
我也这么想
Yeah, me too.
这就走吗
Leaving so soon?
我们还没来得及庆祝呢
We haven't even had a chance to celebrate.
嗯  那你自己庆祝吧
Yeah. Well, you can celebrate without me.
你不是要对我撒气吧
You're not gonna get all pouty on me now, are you?
拜托
Come on.
你今天杀了俩恶魔
You killed two demons today.
嗯  或许你不在乎  但我也杀了俩人类
Yeah. Well, maybe you don't care, but I killed two humans too.
萨姆  你清楚恶魔附身人类的结果
Sam, you know what happens when demons piggyback humans.
人类会被利用得身心俱疲
They leave them rode hard and put up wet.
那俩极可能会死得缓慢又痛苦
Chances are those two would've died a slow, sticky death.
你八成是帮他们解脱了
You probably did them a favor.
帮他们解脱
Did them a favor?
你真是个冷酷的贱人
You're a cold bitch, you know that?
本冷酷贱人
Yeah, and this cold bitch
可救了你好几次了
has saved your ass a couple of times now.
是不是尊重我点
Some respect might be nice.
尤其是
Especially
如果你希望我帮你为迪恩解围
if you want me to help you out with Dean and his little problem.
知道吗  你总拿那个吊着我
You know what, you keep dangling that,
但据我所知  迪恩还是要下地狱
but last I checked Dean's still going to hell.
凡事急不得  萨姆
Everything in its own time, Sam.
但我们要等价交换  我们身处战争中
But there's a quid pro quo here. We're in a war.
对  但不知为何  你站在我们这边
Right. But for some reason you're fighting on our team.
告诉我  这是为什么
Now, tell me, why is that again?
去你的
Go screw yourself,
- 就因为这个  - 好啊
- that's why. - I see.
我不需要对你解释我的行为  萨姆
I don't have to justify my actions to you, Sam.
如果你不要我帮忙
If you don't want my help...
好啊
fine.
那把枪给我
Then give me the gun,
我会把它给愿意用它的人
and I'll pass it on to someone who will use it.
或许我就拿它崩了你呢
Maybe I'll just use it on you.
来啊  如果那让你开心
Go ahead, if that makes you happy.
但这可帮不了迪恩
It's not gonna do much for Dean, though.
你打算怎么办
So, what's it gonna be?
这就对了
That's my boy.
这不会轻松的  萨姆
This won't be easy, Sam.
你得做一些
You're gonna have to do things
有违你温柔天性的事
that go against that gentle nature of yours.
还会有附带伤害
There'll be collateral damage.
但这无法避免
But it has to be done.
我不非得喜欢那么做
I don't have to like it.
是啊
No.
你如果喜欢就不是你了
You wouldn't be Sam if you did.
但好的一面是
But on the bright side...
我也会陪伴你
I'll be there with you.
你肩膀上的小堕落天使
That little fallen angel on your shoulder.